{"studentUsername":"velvet","examId":1732190990929,"examName":"MC","courseId":"MATH1000","answerList":["A","A","C"],"scoreList":[10,10,0],"questionObjectList":[{"question":"MC","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190875889},{"question":"MC2","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190878849},{"question":"MC3","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190882208}],"score":20,"fullScore":30,"numberOfCorrect":2,"timeSpend":4,"mcScore":20,"mcFullScore":30,"tfScore":0,"tfFullScore":0,"sqScore":0,"sqFullScore":0,"sqQuestionList":[],"sqAnswerList":[],"sqFullScoreList":[],"graded":false,"id":1732191106896}
{"studentUsername":"velvet","examId":1732191002195,"examName":"MMC","courseId":"MATH1000","answerList":["BD","AD","AC"],"scoreList":[0,0,10],"questionObjectList":[{"question":"MMC","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190899896},{"question":"MMC2","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190917922},{"question":"MMC3","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190923683}],"score":10,"fullScore":30,"numberOfCorrect":1,"timeSpend":7,"mcScore":10,"mcFullScore":30,"tfScore":0,"tfFullScore":0,"sqScore":0,"sqFullScore":0,"sqQuestionList":[],"sqAnswerList":[],"sqFullScoreList":[],"graded":false,"id":1732191118983}
{"studentUsername":"velvet","examId":1732191020607,"examName":"TF","courseId":"MATH1000","answerList":["T","F","T"],"scoreList":[10,0,10],"questionObjectList":[{"question":"TF","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190935182},{"question":"TF2","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190940004},{"question":"TF3","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190944682}],"score":20,"fullScore":30,"numberOfCorrect":2,"timeSpend":4,"mcScore":0,"mcFullScore":0,"tfScore":20,"tfFullScore":30,"sqScore":0,"sqFullScore":0,"sqQuestionList":[],"sqAnswerList":[],"sqFullScoreList":[],"graded":false,"id":1732191127966}
{"studentUsername":"velvet","examId":1732191028681,"examName":"SQ","courseId":"MATH1000","answerList":["123","QAZ","EDC"],"scoreList":[0,0,10],"questionObjectList":[{"question":"SQ1","answer":"QAZ","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190955162},{"question":"SQ2","answer":"WSX","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190963180},{"question":"SQ3","answer":"EDC","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190968879}],"score":10,"fullScore":30,"numberOfCorrect":1,"timeSpend":8,"mcScore":0,"mcFullScore":0,"tfScore":0,"tfFullScore":0,"sqScore":10,"sqFullScore":30,"sqQuestionList":["SQ1","SQ2","SQ3"],"sqAnswerList":["123","QAZ","EDC"],"sqFullScoreList":[10,10,10],"graded":false,"id":1732191139793}
{"studentUsername":"velvet","examId":1732191049283,"examName":"MC+TF","courseId":"MATH1000","answerList":["A","B","D","F","T","T"],"scoreList":[10,0,0,0,10,10],"questionObjectList":[{"question":"MC","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190875889},{"question":"MC2","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190878849},{"question":"MC3","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190882208},{"question":"TF","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190935182},{"question":"TF2","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190940004},{"question":"TF3","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190944682}],"score":30,"fullScore":60,"numberOfCorrect":3,"timeSpend":9,"mcScore":10,"mcFullScore":30,"tfScore":20,"tfFullScore":30,"sqScore":0,"sqFullScore":0,"sqQuestionList":[],"sqAnswerList":[],"sqFullScoreList":[],"graded":false,"id":1732191152267}
{"studentUsername":"velvet","examId":1732191057511,"examName":"TF+SQ","courseId":"MATH1000","answerList":["T","T","T","QAZ","WSX","EDC"],"scoreList":[10,10,10,10,10,10],"questionObjectList":[{"question":"TF","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190935182},{"question":"TF2","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190940004},{"question":"TF3","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190944682},{"question":"SQ1","answer":"QAZ","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190955162},{"question":"SQ2","answer":"WSX","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190963180},{"question":"SQ3","answer":"EDC","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190968879}],"score":60,"fullScore":60,"numberOfCorrect":6,"timeSpend":11,"mcScore":0,"mcFullScore":0,"tfScore":30,"tfFullScore":30,"sqScore":30,"sqFullScore":30,"sqQuestionList":["SQ1","SQ2","SQ3"],"sqAnswerList":["QAZ","WSX","EDC"],"sqFullScoreList":[10,10,10],"graded":false,"id":1732191166649}
{"studentUsername":"velvet","examId":1732191075112,"examName":"MC+SQ","courseId":"MATH1000","answerList":["D","A","B","","",""],"scoreList":[0,10,0,0,0,0],"questionObjectList":[{"question":"MC","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190875889},{"question":"MC2","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190878849},{"question":"MC3","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190882208},{"question":"SQ1","answer":"QAZ","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190955162},{"question":"SQ2","answer":"WSX","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190963180},{"question":"SQ3","answer":"EDC","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190968879}],"score":10,"fullScore":60,"numberOfCorrect":1,"timeSpend":7,"mcScore":10,"mcFullScore":30,"tfScore":0,"tfFullScore":0,"sqScore":0,"sqFullScore":30,"sqQuestionList":["SQ1","SQ2","SQ3"],"sqAnswerList":["","",""],"sqFullScoreList":[10,10,10],"graded":false,"id":1732191177728}
{"studentUsername":"velvet","examId":1732191083059,"examName":"All","courseId":"MATH1000","answerList":[null,null,null,"","","",null,null,null,"","",""],"scoreList":[0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0],"questionObjectList":[{"question":"MC","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190875889},{"question":"MC2","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190878849},{"question":"MC3","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190882208},{"question":"MMC","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190899896},{"question":"MMC2","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190917922},{"question":"MMC3","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190923683},{"question":"TF","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190935182},{"question":"TF2","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190940004},{"question":"TF3","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190944682},{"question":"SQ1","answer":"QAZ","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190955162},{"question":"SQ2","answer":"WSX","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190963180},{"question":"SQ3","answer":"EDC","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190968879}],"score":0,"fullScore":120,"numberOfCorrect":0,"timeSpend":3,"mcScore":0,"mcFullScore":60,"tfScore":0,"tfFullScore":30,"sqScore":0,"sqFullScore":30,"sqQuestionList":["SQ1","SQ2","SQ3"],"sqAnswerList":["","",""],"sqFullScoreList":[10,10,10],"graded":false,"id":1732191184498}
